John Alden Mason Papers 1904-1967 Mss.B.M384
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1926-1967; 20 linear feet
  - American Anthropologist (Box 1)
    - Johnson, Frederick (Box 4)
    - Johnson, Jotham (Box 4)
    - Johnson, Nelson T (Box 4)
    - Johnson, Olga (Box 4)
    - Jovita, Maria (Box 4)
    - Judd, Neil M (Box 4)
    - Junek, Oscar Waldemar (Box 4)
    - Kaempffert, Waldemar (Box 4)
    - Kaplan, Jeremiah (Box 4)
    - Kelso de Montigny, Alan H (Box 4)
    - Kennard, Edward A (Box 4)
    - Kennedy, Ramond (Box 4)
    - Ketchum, Miriam Blaisdale (Box 4)
    - Kidder, A V (Box 4)
    - Kiell, Norman (Box 4)
    - Kilburn, Peter C (Box 4)
    - Klodic, R (Box 4)
    - Kluckhohn, Clyde (Box 4)
    - Ko, S F (Box 4)
    - Koppers, W (Box 4)
    - Krieger, Alexander (Box 4)
    - Kroeber, Alfred L (Box 4)
    - Krogman, W M (Box 4)
    - Lévi-Strauss, Claude (Box 4)
    - La Barre, Weston (Box 4)
    - Ladigenski, A M (Box 4)
    - Lapp, C J (Box 4)
    - Lasker, Bruno (Box 4)
    - Lasker, Gabriel (Box 4)
    - Latimer, Wendell M (Box 4)
    - Laughlin, William S (Box 4)
    - Leacock, Eleanor (Box 4)
    - Leech, MacEdward (Box 4)
    - Leighton, A H (Box 4)
    - Lepatin, Ivan A (Box 4)
    - Leslie, Vernon (Box 4)
    - Lessa, William A (Box 4)
    - Lesser, Alexander (Box 4)
    - Lewis, Gilbert N (Box 4)
    - Lewis, Oscar (Box 4)
    - Lewis, T M N (Box 4)
    - Library of Congress-Photoduplication (Box 4)
    - Lightfoot, Virginia Dorsey (Box 4)
    - Linguistic Soc. of America (Box 4)
      - Bloch, Bernard (Box 4)
    - Linné, Sigvald (Box 4)
    - Linton, Ralph (Box 4)
    - Little, K L (Box 4)
    - Livingston, Howard N (Box 4)
    - Loeb, Edwin M (Box 4)
    - Logan, Robert A (Box 4)
    - London School of Education (Box 4)
    - Longyear, John M III (Box 4)
    - Lothrop, Samuel K (Box 4)
    - Loughborough, John L (Box 4)
    - Lounsbury, Floyd G (Box 4)
    - Lowie, Robert H (Box 4)
    - Luomala, Katherine (Box 4)
    - Luzac and Co., Publishers (Box 4)
    - MacCurdy, George Grant (Box 4)
    - MacDougald, Duncan, Jr (Box 4)
    - Macgowan, Kenneth (Box 4)
    - Macgregor, Gordon (Box 4)
    - Macmillan Company (Box 4)
    - Majumdar, D N (Box 4)
    - Mamchur, Stephen W (Box 4)
    - Mandelbaum, David G (Box 4)
    - Mangin, William P (Box 4)
    - Manning, T H (Box 4)
    - Marshall, Donald S (Box 4)
    - Martin, George C (Box 4)
    - Mason, Leonard (Box 4)
    - McCormick, T C (Box 4)
    - McCown, Theodore D (Box 4)
    - McDavid, Raven I Jr (Box 4)
    - McKern, W C (Box 4)
    - McNickle, D'Arcy (Box 4)
    - McPhillamey, Marjorie (Box 4)
    - Mead, Margaret (Box 4)
    - Means, Mrs. Louise M (Box 4)
    - Meggers, Betty J (Box 4)
    - Mellen, Ida M (Box 4)
    - Mengin, Ernst (Box 4)
    - Mental Measurements Yearbook (Box 4)
    - Merrill, E D (Box 4)
    - Metraux, A (Box 5)
    - Mexico. Oficina de Correspondencia y Archivos (Box 5)
    - Miller, L G (Box 5)
    - Mirov, N T (Box 5)
    - Montagu, M F Ashley (Box 5)
    - Montigny, Alan H Kelso de (Box 5)
    - Mook, Maurice A (Box 5)
    - Mordini, Antonio (Box 5)
    - Morley, Sylvanus G (Box 5)
    - Morris, Albert (Box 5)
    - Movius, Hallam L Jr (Box 5)
    - Muensterberger, Warren (Box 5)
    - Munksgaard, Einar (Box 5)
    - Murdock, George P (Box 5)
    - Murra, John (Box 5)
    - Muses, Charles A (Box 5)
    - Musgrave, John (Box 5)
    - Nabrink, G (Box 5)
    - Narducci, Guglielmo (Box 5)
    - Naturalist's Directory (Box 5)
    - Nelson, N C (Box 5)
    - Nichols, Arthur B (Box 5)
    - Noguera, Eduardo (Box 5)
    - Noon, John (Box 5)
    - Noyes, Robert G (Box 5)
    - Oberg, Kalervo (Box 5)
    - O'Bryan, Deric (Box 5)
    - Opler, Morris Edward (Box 5)
    - Oregon Historical Society (Box 5)
    - Orr, Kenneth G (Box 5)
    - Osborne, Douglas (Box 5)
    - Osgood, Cornelius (Box 5)
    - Oxford University Press (Box 5)
    - Pérez de la Rive, Francisco (Box 5)
    - Palmer, Ernest J (Box 5)
    - Parsons, Talcott (Box 5)
    - Passin, Herbert (Box 5)
    - Patai, Raphael (Box 5)
    - Pavia, Mario N (Box 5)
    - Pelzel, John C (Box 5)
    - Petrullo, V M (Box 5)
    - Phillips, Wendell (Box 5)
    - Pike, Kenneth L (Box 5)
    - Pollenz, Philippa (Box 5)
    - Posthumus, N W (Box 5)
    - Powdermaker, Hortense (Box 5)
    - Powell, Lawrence Clark (Box 5)
    - Price, Maurice T (Box 5)
    - Proskouriakoff, Tatiana (Box 5)
    - Quimby, George I (Box 5)
    - Radcliffe-Brown, A R (Box 5)
    - Random House, Inc (Box 5)
    - Ray, Verne F (Box 5)
    - re Nesbitt, Paul (Box 5)
    - Reed, Charles A (Box 5)
    - Reed, Erik K (Box 5)
    - Reichard, Gladys A (Box 5)
    - Reichel-Dolmatoff, G (Box 5)
    - Reprint Orders (Box 5)
      - Newman, Marshall T (Box 5)
      - Nussbaum, William (Box 5)
      - Rietz, Robert (Box 5)
      - Shade, Charles I (Box 5)
      - Schufelt, Lynn (Box 5)
      - Scuham, Paula (Box 5)
      - The Southwest Museum (Box 5)
      - Ottenburg, Simon (Box 5)
      - White, Majorie (Box 5)
    - Rhodes-Livingstone Institute (Box 5)
    - Riesenfeld, Alphonse (Box 5)
    - Ritchie, William A (Box 5)
    - Roberts, Frank H. H., Jr (Box 5)
    - Robinson-Rapp Advertising Agency (Box 5)
    - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 5)
    - Roheim, Geza (Box 5)
    - Rojas, Alfonso Villa (Box 5)
    - Rose, Frederick G. G (Box 5)
    - Rouse, Irving (Box 5)
    - Rousseau, Jacques (Box 5)
    - Rowe, John H (Box 5)
    - Royal Anthropological Institute (Box 5)
    - Royal Anthropological Institute (Box 5)
    - Runeberg, Arne (Box 5)
    - Sameth, Sigmund (Box 5)
    - Sampson, Sidney Post (Box 5)
    - Sanders, Irwin T (Box 5)
    - Sankalia, H D (Box 5)
    - Sauer, Carl O (Box 5)
    - Saunders. W. B. Saunders Co (Box 5)
    - Schaefer, John (Box 5)
    - Schaeffer, Claude E (Box 5)
    - Scheben, L H D (Box 5)
    - Schmitt, Karl (Box 5)
    - Schroer, Gilbert W (Box 5)
    - Scott, Donald (Box 5)
    - Scott, Donald (Box 5)
    - Scott, Robert Harold (Box 5)
    - Sebeok, Thomas A (Box 5)
    - Setzler, F M (Box 5)
    - Shaffer, Kenneth R (Box 5)
    - Shapiro, Harry L (Box 5)
    - Shay, Phillip Wendell (Box 5)
    - Shetrone, H C (Box 5)
    - Shetrone, H C (Box 5)
    - Sibley, Elbridge (Box 5)
    - Siegel, Bernard J (Box 5)
    - Simmons, Leo W (Box 5)
    - Simpson, George E (Box 5)
    - Sleight, Frederick W (Box 5)
    - Sloan. William Sloan Associates (Box 5)
    - Slotkin, J S (Box 5)
    - Smith, Harvey L (Box 5)
    - Smith, Marian W (Box 5)
    - Snowden, Frank M Jr (Box 5)
    - Sociěté des Océanistes (Box 5)
    - Soule, Phelps (Box 5)
    - Southeast Asia Institute (Box 5)
    - Spencer, Dorothy M (Box 5)
    - Spencer, Robert F (Box 5)
    - Spier, Franklin Spier, Inc (Box 5)
    - Spier, Leslie (Box 5)
    - Spoehr, Alexander (Box 5)
    - Stanisawski, Dan and Doris (Box 5)
    - Stechert-Hafner, Inc (Box 5)
    - Stevens, L C (Box 5)
    - Steward, Julian H (Box 5)
    - Stewart, Kenneth M (Box 5)
    - Stewart, T D (Box 5)
    - Stimson, Anna (Box 5)
    - Stohlman, W F (Box 5)
    - Stout, David B (Box 5)
    - Stovall, J Willis (Box 5)
    - Straley, Wilson (Box 5)
    - Strong, E W (Box 5)
    - Strong, William Duncan (Box 5)
    - Stroup, Herbert H (Box 5)
    - Summers, Paul L (Box 5)
    - Swadesh, Morris (Box 5)
    - Swanton, John R (Box 5)
    - Swanton, John R (Box 5)
    - Tatum, Robert M (Box 5)
    - Tax, Sol (Box 5)
    - Taylor, Douglas (Box 5)
    - Taylor, Jay L B (Box 5)
    - Taylor, Pauline (Box 5)
    - Taylor, Walter Willard, Jr (Box 5)
    - Terra, Helmut de (Box 5)
    - Terry, Robert J (Box 5)
    - The Polynesian Society (Box 5)
    - The Scottish Anthropological and Folklore Soc (Box 5)
    - The Viking Fund, Inc (Box 5)
    - The Woman's Missionary Soc. of the United Church of Canada (Box 5)
    - Thompson, Alden F (Box 5)
    - Thompson, Clem O (Box 5)
    - Thompson, Eric (Box 5)
    - Thompson, Laura (Box 5)
    - Thompson, Lawrence S (Box 5)
    - Thompson, Stith (Box 5)
    - Time, Inc (Box 5)
    - Titiev, Mischa (Box 5)
    - Tozzer, Alfred M (Box 5)
    - Trager, Mrs. Helen (Box 5)
    - Travel Agent., Herb Stoeckel (Box 5)
    - Treganza, Adan E (Box 5)
    - Tschopil, Harry, Jr (Box 5)
    - Tumin, Melvin M (Box 5)
    - Turner Subscription Agency, Inc (Box 5)
    - Turney-High, Harry (Box 5)
    - U.S.S.R. All Union Geographic Society (Box 6)
    - Underhill, Ruth (Box 6)
    - Underwood, Frances W (Box 6)
    - United Nations (Box 6)
      - Allen, Paul S (Box 6)
      - Métraux, A (Box 6)
    - United States. Dept. of Labor (Box 6)
    - University of Chicago (Box 6)
    - University of Michigan (Box 6)
    - University of Oklahoma Press (Box 6)
    - University of Oklahoma (Box 6)
    - University of South Carolina (Box 6)
    - Useem, John H (Box 6)
    - Van Nostrand Company (Box 6)
    - Van Rensselaer, Alexander (Box 6)
    - Vassar College (Box 6)
    - Verdoorn, Frans (Box 6)
    - Vienna. Museum für Völkenkunde (Box 6)
    - Villa Rojas, Alfonso (Box 6)
    - Viv˘o, Jorge A (Box 6)
    - Voegelin, Carl (Box 6)
    - Voegelin, Erminie Wheeler (Box 6)
    - Vogt, E Z (Box 6)
    - Vowles, R (Box 6)
    - Wagley, Charles (Box 6)
    - Wagley, Charles (Box 6)
    - Wallace, William J (Box 6)
    - Wallis, David E (Box 6)
    - Wallis, Wilson D (Box 6)
    - Walter, Paul A F (Box 6)
    - Ward, B E (Box 6)
    - Washburn, S. L (Box 6)
    - Wassén, Henry (Box 6)
    - Waterman, Richard A (Box 6)
    - Watson, James B (Box 6)
    - Waverly Press, Inc (Box 6)
    - Weeks, Donald (Box 6)
    - Weidenreich, Franz (Box 6)
    - Weitlander, Robert J (Box 6)
    - Weitzner, Bella (Box 6)
    - Weltfish, Gene (Box 6)
    - Wessel, Bessie Bloom (Box 6)
    - White, H. A (Box 6)
    - White, Leslie A (Box 6)
    - Wieschoff, H A (Box 6)
    - Wildoner, Dale E (Box 6)
    - Wiley, John, & Sons (Box 6)
    - Wilkes, Daniel (Box 6)
    - Will, George W (Box 6)
    - Williams, A. F (Box 6)
    - Williams, Elgin (Box 6)
    - Wilson. H. W. Wilson Co (Box 6)
    - Wissler, Clark (Box 6)
    - Wissler, Mary (Box 6)
    - Witthoft, John (Box 6)
    - Wolfe, A B (Box 6)
    - Wonderly, William L (Box 6)
    - Wood, Calvin D (Box 6)
    - Woods, Carter A (Box 6)
    - Woodward, Carol H (Box 6)
    - Worman, Eugene C., Jr (Box 6)
    - Wormington, H. M (Box 6)
    - Wyman, Leland C (Box 6)
    - Yale University Press (Box 6)
    - Zaichick, Norman (Box 6)
    - Zane, Arlene Bonos (Box 6)
  - American Anthropologist (Box 6)
    - Barrett, S. A (Box 6)
    - Gehner, R. F (Box 6)
    - Gifford, E. W (Box 6)
    - Herskovits, Melville J (Box 6)
    - Highland, Genevieve A (Box 6)
    - Hooton, Ernest A (Box 6)
    - Klodic, R (Box 6)
    - Lawler, Joseph J (Box 6)
    - Linton, Adeline (Box 6)
    - Linton, Ralph (Box 6)
    - Loeb, Mrs (Box 6)
    - Lowie, Robert H (Box 6)
    - Maxham, Frederick B (Box 6)
    - Morgan, Richard G (Box 6)
    - Perry, Margaret E (Box 6)
    - Sapir, Edward (Box 6)
    - Sehnert, Marion P (Box 6)
    - Setzler, Frank M (Box 6)
    - Spier, Leslie (Box 6)
    - Spindler, George D (Box 6)
    - Stout, D B (Box 6)
    - Swanton, John R (Box 6)
    - Taylor, Charles J (Box 6)
    - Taylor, Councill (Box 6)
    - U.S. Post Office Dept (Box 6)
    - Voegelin, Erminie (Box 6)
    - White, Leslie (Box 6)
  - American Antiquity (Box 6)
    - Bell, Robert E (Box 6)
  - American Association for the Advanceme of Science (Box 6)
    - Campbell, F L (Box 6)
    - Kelly, J Charles (Box 6)
    - Livingston, Burton E (Box 6)
    - Satterthwaite, Linton, Jr (Box 6)
    - Smith, Victor J (Box 6)
    - Terry, R J (Box 6)
    - Witham, Dorothy (Box 6)
    - Woodley, Sam (Box 6)
  - American Association for the Advanceme of Science. Section H (Box 6)
  - American Association of Museums (Box 6)
  - American Association of Museums (Box 6)
    - Coleman, Laurence Vale (Box 6)
    - Hatherick, Helen Works (Box 6)
  - American Book Center for War Devasted Libraries, Inc (Box 6)
  - American Consular Service (Box 6)
    - Bowman. Thomas D (Box 6)
    - Eaton, E W (Box 6)
    - Linton (Box 6)
    - Park, Nelson R (Box 6)
    - Satterthorn (Box 6)
    - Wormuth, Romeyn (Box 6)
  - American Council of Learned Sciences (Box 6)
    - Cooper, John M (Box 6)
    - Leland, Waldo G (Box 6)
  - American Council of Learned Societies (Box 6)
    Re: Frederica de Laguna
  - American Council on Education. Committee on Graduate Instruction (Box 6)
    - Hughes, R M (Box 6)
  - American Ethnological Society, Inc (Box 6)
    - Anton y Ferrandia, Manuel (Box 6)
    - Barres, Francisco de la (Box 6)
    - Lesser, Alexander (Box 6)
  - American Folklore Society (Box 6)
    - Ashton, J W (Box 6)
    - Leach, MacEdward (Box 6)
    - Opler, Morris E (Box 6)
    - Thompson, Stith (Box 6)
    - Weltfish, Gene (Box 6)
  - American Friends Service Committee (Box 6)
    - Timbres, Rebecca J (Box 6)
    - Wilbur, Walter (Box 6)
  - American Geographical Society (Box 7)
  - American Indian Languages (Box 7)
  - American Indian Museum (Box 7)
    - Newell, William B (Box 7)
  - American Notes and Queries (Box 7)
    - Pilkington, Walter (Box 7)
  - American Philosophical Society (Box 7)
    - Conklin, Edwin Grant (Box 7)
    - Eisenhart, Luther P (Box 7)
    - Hess, Gertrude D (Box 7)
    - Lingelbach, William E (Box 7)
    - Noonan, Julia A (Box 7)
  - American Philosophical Society. Library (Box 7)
  - American Philosophical Society. Obituary of A.V. Kidder (Box 7)
  - American Scientist (Box 7)
  - American Section: Tentative list of rarest (Box 7)
  - Americans for Democratic Action. Tours objects to be packed in case of danger (Box 7)
  - Americas (Box 7)
  - Amram, David Werner (Box 7)
  - Amaram, D. W., Jr (Box 7)
  - Amram, David, Jr (Box 7)
  - Ancient Civilizations of Middle America (Box 7)
  - Ancient Civilizations of Peru (Box 7)
  - Andean Civilization (Box 7)
  - Anderson, A. E (Box 7)
  - Anderson, A. T (Box 7)
  - Anderson, Edgar (Box 7)
    - Missouri Botanical Garden (Box 7)
  - Anderson, George A (Box 7)
  - Andrade, Manuel J (Box 7)
  - Andrews, E Wyllis (Box 7)
  - Angell, William R (Box 7)
    - Sutherland, William M (Box 7)
  - Angle, Paula (Box 7)
  - Angulo Valdes, Carlos (Box 7)
  - Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science (Box 7)
    - Charlesworth, James C (Box 7)
    - Logan, E B (Box 7)
    - Valentine, Edith (Box 7)
  - Annis, Fred V (Box 7)
  - Antevs, Ernst (Box 7)
  - Anthropology curriculum study project (Box 7)
  - Anthropology in 1939 (Box 7)
  - Antze, G (Box 7)
  - Aoust, Enrique d' (Box 7)
  - Apgar, C. S (Box 7)
  - Appel, Ludwig (Box 7)
  - Appell, George N (Box 7)
  - Archaeological Society of New Jersey (Box 7)
  - Archaeological work, NY (Box 8)
  - Archaeology, Mrs. Weinburg, editor (Box 8)
  - Archaeology - Local - 1954 Museum local excavations (Box 8)
  - Archaeology as a career (Box 8)
  - Archeologia (Box 8)
  - Archeological Institute of America (Box 8)
    - Luce, Stephen B (Box 8)
    - Seiglie, Oscar (Box 8)
  - Archeological Society of Delaware (Box 8)
  - Archeological Society of Delaware (Box 8)
    - Crozier, Archibald (Box 8)
  - Archeological Society of New Jersey (Box 8)
    - Campbell, Earl F (Box 8)
    - Cross, Dorothy (Box 8)
    - Greywacz, Kathryn B (Box 8)
    - Naylor, Francis (Box 8)
    - Pearsall, Leigh M (Box 8)
    - Standard Printing Co (Box 8)
  - Armer, Laura Adams (Box 8)
  - Armillas, Pedro (Box 8)
  - Armstrong, May (Box 8)
  - Arnold, Mary Ellicott (Box 8)
  - Aroaya, Pedro Manuel (Box 8)
  - Arosemena, Emiliano (Box 8)
  - Arpee, Levon Harris (Box 8)
  - Arrington, J Earl (Box 8)
  - Arthur, Mary (Box 8)
  - Article for Pennsylvania Archaeologist. (Box 8)
  - Article for Osborne's Handbook of Guatemala (Box 8)
  - Article on Santorem.. (Box 8)
  - Ashenden, C (Box 8)
  - Atcheson, Mrs. Thomas J (Box 8)
  - Atcheson, T. J (Box 8)
  - Atherton, Grant S (Box 8)
  - Attix, C. Thomas (Box 8)
  - Atwood, Robert E (Box 8)
  - Atwood, W. L (Box 8)
  - August, D. Frederick (Box 8)
  - Augustin, J. J (Box 8)
  - Austin, W (Box 8)
  - Avendaño, P Frank (Box 8)
  - Avinoff, A (Box 8)
    - Carnegie Museum, Pittsburgh (Box 8)
    - Holland, W J (Box 8)
  - Axton, E D (Box 8)
  - Bügenhagen, Karl Horst (Box 8)
  - Babb, N J (Box 8)
  - Babcock, Mrs. Bernie (Box 8)
  - Bach, Otto K (Box 8)
  - Bache, Charles (Box 8)
  - Bachus, R C (Box 8)
  - Baerreis, David A (Box 8)
  - Bagoria, Natalie Y (Box 8)
  - Bahlmann, Fr. Amandus (Box 8)
  - Bailey, E H Co (Box 8)
  - Bailey, Lucille (Box 8)
  - Baillou, Renate (Box 8)
  - Baily, R. W (Box 8)
  - Baily, Robert William (Box 8)
  - Baker, Miss (Box 8)
  - Baker, M. Louise (Box 8)
  - Baldus, Herbert (Box 8)
  - Ballard, Mrs. Frances S (Box 8)
  - Banks, Miriam A (Box 8)
  - Banta, George, Publishing Co (Box 8)
    - Brandhorn, F R (Box 8)
    - Densmore, Frances (Box 8)
    - Frick, Scilda C (Box 8)
    - Gilbert, William H (Box 8)
    - Hause, Helen H (Box 8)
    - Peerenboom, C A (Box 8)
  - Banta, George, Publishing Company (Box 8)
  - Barata, Frederico (Box 8)
  - Barbachano, Fernando (Box 8)
  - Barbeau, Marius (Box 8)
    - Fejos, Paul (Box 8)
  - Bardin, James C (Box 8)
  - Barenkopf, Dorothy S (Box 8)
  - Barnes, Albert C (Box 8)
  - Barnes, Dana A (Box 8)
  - Barnett, Homer (Box 8)
  - Barrell, Lloyd (Box 9)
  - Barrenechea, Raúl Porras (Box 9)
  - Barrera Vásquez, Alfredo (Box 9)
  - Barrett, Charles (Box 9)
  - Barrett, Mary X (Box 9)
  - Barrett, S. A (Box 9)
  - Barringer, Brandon (Box 9)
    - Bailey, Bill (Box 9)
  - Barry, J. Neilson (Box 9)
  - Bartlett, Katherine (Box 9)
  - Bartlett, Robert E., Jr (Box 9)
  - Bartlett, Scott (Box 9)
  - Barton, R. Paul (Box 9)
  - Barton, William J (Box 9)
  - Basadre, Jorge (Box 9)
    - Pizarro Z, Gonzalo (Box 9)
  - Bascom, Burton W., 1947-1960; 3 folders (Box 9)
  - Bascom, William R (Box 9)
  - Bass, George Warrington (Box 9)
    - Morley, Sylvanus G (Box 9)
  - Bataafsche Petroleum Maatschappij (Box 9)
  - Batchelder, Ernest A (Box 9)
  - Batiza, Ignacio L (Box 9)
  - Battistessa, Angel J (Box 9)
  - Bauernfeind, A W (Box 9)
  - Baufield, Sister Mary Imelda (Box 9)
  - Baugh, Albert C (Box 9)
  - Baughan, J L (Box 9)
  - Baughman, Homer L (Box 9)
  - Beach, James E (Box 9)
  - Beals, Ralph L (Box 9)
  - Beasley, R. M (Box 9)
  - Beatty, Willard V (Box 9)
  - Les Beaux Arts (Box 9)
    - White, Charlotte F (Box 9)
  - Beck, Charles M., Jr (Box 9)
  - Beckman, Sarah (Box 9)
  - Beckwith, Frank (Box 9)
  - Beggs, Virginia (Box 9)
  - Beidler, Paul (Box 9)
    - Johnson, E R Fennimore (Box 9)
    - Madeira, Percy C Jr (Box 9)
  - Beimler, Theodore F (Box 9)
  - Belknap, Maitland (Box 9)
  - Bell, E. H (Box 9)
  - Bell, Enid (Box 9)
  - Bell, Harry L (Box 9)
  - Bell, Robert R., editor (Box 9)
  - Belli, Ernesto (Box 9)
  - Belloc, Francisco Arellano (Box 9)
  - Belmont, G. E (Box 9)
  - Bender, Byron W (Box 9)
  - Benedict, Ruth (Box 9)
    - American Ethnological Society (Box 9)
    - Smith, Marian (Box 9)
  - Benn, George F (Box 9)
  - Bennett, Helen M (Box 9)
  - Bennett, Keith (Box 9)
  - Bennett, Wendell C (Box 9)
  - Bennyhoff, J. A (Box 9)
  - Bentz, Walter Cosby (Box 9)
  - Bergdoll, Erwin (Box 9)
  - Bergendahl, Haldor (Box 9)
  - Berger, Mrs. David (Box 9)
  - Bergman, Edward J (Box 9)
  - Bergsoe, Paul (Box 9)
  - Berlin, Heinrich (Box 9)
  - Bernal, Ignacio (Box 9)
  - Bernays, Edward L (Box 9)
  - Berney, Hoffman (Box 9)
  - Bernhard, Harry M (Box 9)
  - Berro, Román (Box 9)
  - Berry, Brewton (Box 9)
  - Bessac, Mrs. Susanne L (Box 9)
  - Besserman, H R (Box 9)
  - Best, William R (Box 9)
  - Bevan, Bernard (Box 9)
  - Beyer, Edna (Box 9)
  - Beyer, Hermann (Box 9)
  - Biase, Attilio de (Box 9)
  - Bierhenke, Wilhelm (Box 9)
  - Bijur, George (Box 9)
  - Bilden, Rüdiger (Box 9)
  - Bingham, Ernestine (Box 9)
  - Bingham, Millicent Todd (Box 9)
  - Binns, Lita S (Box 9)
  - Biographical Directory of American Men of Science (Box 9)
    - Cattell, Jacques (Box 9)
  - Bird, Junius (Box 9)
  - Birk, Martha M (Box 9)
  - Birket-Smith, Kaj (Box 9)
  - Birney, Hoffman (Box 9)
  - Birrell, Verla (Box 9)
  - Bischof, Henning (Box 9)
  - Bissell, Barbara M (Box 9)
  - Bitner, Ruth (Box 9)
  - Black, Fred L (Box 9)
    - Barbachano, F A (Box 9)
    - Gamio, Manuel (Box 9)
    - Kidder, A V (Box 9)
    - MacPhail, Neil P (Box 9)
    - Molina, Adolfo (Box 9)
    - Morley, Sylvanus G (Box 9)
    - Osborne, E A (Box 9)
    - Smith, Robert E (Box 9)
  - Black, Glenn A (Box 9)
    - Johnson, Frederick (Box 9)
  - Blackwell, Mrs. T J (Box 9)
  - Blaine, B C (Box 9)
  - Blake, A. M (Box 9)
  - Blaker, Margaret C (Box 9)
  - Blakeslee, Howard (Box 9)
  - Blanchet, Guy H (Box 9)
  - Blanco, Tomás (Box 9)
  - Blanshard, A R (Box 9)
  - Bleiler, Max (Box 9)
  - Bliss, Wesley L (Box 9)
    - Howard, Edgar B (Box 9)
  - Blixen, Olaf (Box 9)
  - Blocker, John C (Box 9)
  - Blom, Frans (Box 9)
  - Blue, Samuel (Chief) (Box 9)
  - Blumensohn, Jules (Box 9)
  - Boas, Franz (Box 10)
    - Jayne, Horace (Box 10)
    - Sapir, Edward (Box 10)
  - Boecklen, Eileen J (Box 10)
  - Boekelman, H J (Box 10)
  - Boericke, Harold (Box 10)
  - Bogata, Colombia. Banco de la Republica (Box 10)
  - Boggs, R. S (Box 10)
  - Bogota, Colombia. Museo de Oro (Box 10)
  - Bogurus, Waldemar G (Box 10)
  - Bohan, Paul R (Box 10)
  - Bohning, W. H (Box 10)
  - Boles, Gene E (Box 10)
  - Bolger, Robert V (Box 10)
  - Bolinder, Gustaf (Box 10)
  - Bolles, John S (Box 10)
  - Bolling, G. M (Box 10)
  - Bolman, F. deW., Jr (Box 10)
  - Bonaventure, Father (Box 10)
    - Voegelin, Carl F (Box 10)
  - Bonavia, Duccio (Box 10)
  - Bonifacio, Romero A (Box 10)
  - Bonilla y S, Guillermo (Box 10)
  - Bonnick, Sydney O (Box 10)
  - Borbolla, F Rubin de la (Box 10)
  - Borhegyi, Stephan F (Box 10)
  - Born, Mary Mercer (Box 10)
  - Born, Wolfgang (Box 10)
  - Bosch-Gimpera, Pedro (Box 10)
  - Bouda, K (Box 10)
    - Satterthwaite, Linton, Jr (Box 10)
  - Boudeman, Donald O (Box 10)
  - Bourgeois, Julia F (Box 10)
  - Bowers, Alfred W (Box 10)
  - Bowles, Gordon T (Box 10)
  - Bowman, Isaiah (Box 10)
  - Boy Scouts of America, Philadelphia (Box 10)
  - Boyar, Francis (Box 10)
  - Boyer, David J (Box 10)
  - Bradbury, Charles H (Box 10)
  - Brainerd, George W (Box 10)
  - Brammer, Mauck (Box 10)
  - Brand, Donald D (Box 10)
  - Brandt, E. N (Box 10)
  - Branegan, James A (Box 10)
  - Braunholtz, H. J (Box 10)
  - Breckenridge, R. W (Box 10)
  - Breeser, Mrs. William G., Jr (Box 10)
  - Breeskin, Adelyn D (Box 10)
  - Breidenstine, A G (Box 10)
  - Brenner, Anita (Box 10)
  - Brett, Henry R (Box 10)
  - Brew, J O (Box 10)
    - Peabody Museum of Archeology & Ethnology. Harvard University (Box 10)
    - Thomas, Iris B (Box 10)
  - Briggs, L. Cabot (Box 10)
  - Briggs, Warren (Box 10)
  - Brigham, Edward M (Box 10)
  - Bright, A Forrest (Box 10)
  - Brinton Memorial Volume (Box 10)
  - Brinton remainders, distribution (Box 10)
  - Brinton, Christian (Box 10)
  - Brinton, Daniel Garrison, Inquiry (Box 10)
    - O'Donnell, Richard J (Box 10)
  - Brinton, Mrs. Daniel G (Box 10)
  - Brinton's Library and Manuscripts (Box 10)
  - Britton, W H (Box 10)
  - Broad, Jennie (Box 10)
    - Kidder, Alfred, II (Box 10)
  - Broadcast: Pan-American Association (Box 10)
  - Brock, Herman G (Box 10)
  - Brock, Mary L. T (Box 10)
  - Brookfield, Robert M (Box 10)
  - Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Sciences (Box 10)
    - Atkins, Charles D (Box 10)
  - Brooklyn Museum (Box 10)
  - Brooks, A. B (Box 10)
  - Brooks, H. E (Box 10)
  - Brooks, Jerome E (Box 10)
  - Brooks, L. T (Box 10)
  - Brooks, Richard H (Box 10)
  - Brooks, Seal T (Box 10)
  - Brown, Allen (Box 10)
  - Brown, Barnum (Box 10)
  - Brown, Dorothy Jean (Box 10)
  - Brown, Elsie (Box 10)
  - Brown, Frederick L (Box 10)
  - Brown, G. Gordon (Box 10)
  - Brown, Harold C (Box 10)
  - Brown, Joseph Epes, III (Box 10)
  - Brown, Monroe N (Box 10)
  - Brown, O. B (Box 10)
  - Brown, W. Norman (Box 10)